<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?>
<plan plan-format="1.0"
      name="EGit"
      xmlns="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan"
      xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
      >
   <release projectid="technology.egit" version="0.6"/>

   <introduction>
     <html:div>
       The EGit project provides two major technologies:
       <html:ul>
         <html:li>
           JGit, a pure Java implementation of the Git version control system.
           The JGit component is licensed under the <html:a href="http://www.eclipse.org/org/documents/edl-v10.php">EDL</html:a>
           and has only BSD licensed dependencies.
         </html:li>
         <html:li>
           EGit, an Eclipse team provider plugin which relies upon JGit to
           access local and remote Git repositories.
         </html:li>
       </html:ul>       
     </html:div>
   </introduction>

   <release_deliverables>
     <html:div>
       Working team provider plugin.
     </html:div>
   </release_deliverables>

   <release_milestones>
      <milestone date="10/30/2009" milestone="M1">
        <html:div>
          The first incubation release of EGit and JGit code from the
          eclipse.org namespace and eclipse.org the download area.
        </html:div>
        <html:div>
          The primary goals of this release are to fix the outstanding data
          corruption documented in <html:a href="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/show_bug.cgi?id=286653">bug 286653</html:a>,
          and to get the project team familiar with the eclipse.org environment
          and development process.   
        </html:div>
        <html:div>
          A secondary goal of this release is to integrate the user-sourced
          wiki documentation as help text, using wikitext.
        </html:div>
      </milestone>
      <milestone date="11/30/2009" milestone="M2">
        <html:div>
          Polish more of the known bugs in the current code, in an effort to
          stablize the code base for the 0.6 release.
        </html:div>      
      </milestone>
      <milestone date="1/1/2010" milestone="0.6">
        <html:div>
          Final 0.6 release available for download through eclipse.org.
          Ideally the EGit project would be out of incubation by this
          point and could make a non-incubation release.
        </html:div>
      </milestone>
   </release_milestones>

   <target_environments>
     <html:div>
       For the EGit team provider, any Java 5 or later platform that runs
       the Eclipse workbench.
     </html:div>
     <html:div>
       For the JGit library, any Java 5 or later standard edition platform,
       without git-core or any other Eclipse product installed.
     </html:div>
     <internationalization>
       <html:div>
         Only English translation files in this release, however all strings
         will be externalized for translation in a future release. 
       </html:div>
     </internationalization>
   </target_environments>

   <compatibility_with_previous_releases>
       <html:div>
         None, EGit has had no prior release under the eclipse.org umbrella.
       </html:div>
       <html:div>
         Compatibility with prior releases made under the org.spearce package
         name will not be considered.  End users must manually uninstall the
         prior feature, install the new one, and reconnect the team provider.
       </html:div>
   </compatibility_with_previous_releases>
</plan>
